

     
MENU TITLE

Webcast: Detecting Insider Threats

SHORT TITLE:

Insider Threats Webcast

PAGE TITLE:     

Webcast: Detecting Insider Threats with Multi-layered Mainframe Security

COPY:

14th September 2017: RSMs Mark Wilson is featured in this IBM Systems Media Webinar with Compuware, taking place on Tuesday, 19 September at 4.00pm BST.

Register and you will learn how to fill the holes that make your mainframe vulnerable, and design a systems and application protection strategy for compliance.

The mainframe is the most securable system in your enterprise, but therein lies its greatest vulnerability: Insider threats. Privileged users gone rogue and impersonators with unauthorized access can easily exploit the business-critical mainframe apps and data you and your customers depend on. Thats a blow to your reputation, and it guarantees expensive penalties for noncompliance with increasingly stringent regulations.

To protect your most valuable assets and ensure compliance, you need intuitive tools even non-mainframe security personnel understand that improve visibility of mainframe activity across the hardware and application levels.

 John Crossno, Principal Product Manager, Compuware features alongside Mark.

You can register here.

LINK:

https://event.webcasts.com/starthere.jsp?ei=1157281&tp_key=3d1e917c85&sti=RSM-invite
